scalemates.com 2017-07-05

# Privacy statement - scale modeling database | stash manager

At scalemates.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by us and how it is used.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at tim@scalemates.com.

__Last Updated: 7th of June 2013

### **Public Nature of Content Submitted to Sites**

The nature of this website is to reach a public audience. Please be aware that any information that you submit to us whether through forms or email, including personally identifiable information, may be publicly displayed on sites hosted at http://www.scalemates.com/, or on websites not within our control. If you don't want others to see such information, don't submit it or make use of the appropriate privacy settings when posting information..

### Membership - Registration

All content is available for registered and non registered users. Registering is free and the amount of data you show in your personal profile is up to you. Your e-Mail address is required but this won't be published on the website, other registered users can however contact you using a contact form.

All other personal information you provide in your personal profile _(except password and eMail)_ will be visible to other users. scalemates.com does not sell, rent or lease its membership lists to third parties.

A user can restrict acces to new messages posted on his wall. New messages can be posted using 3 different privacy settings: "Public", "Mates only" and "Private".

  * Public: Public messages are visible to all registered and non registered users.
  * Mates only: These messages are visible to all the mates of the writer. Mutual agreement is required to become each others mate. 
  * Private: A message marked as private is only visible to 2 members, the sender and the destinee.

Comments on a specific message inherit the privacy settings of the original message

In case comments have been added the privacy settings can only be changed in a more restrictive way. ("Public" to "Mates only", "Public" to "Private", "Mates only" to "Private")

### **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, scalemates.com makes use of log files stored ou our server. The information inside the log files on our servers includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google").

Next to the local logfiles stored on our server we use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"), to better understand how people use our site. Visits to this website are logged by Google Analytics. This analysis is done using the Google analytics service.

scalemates.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by the Google analytics service.

Google Analytics's privacy policy may be found here: [www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html) _(see section 8 for privacy related info)_

### **Cookies and Web Beacons**

scalemates.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising and analysis partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising and analysis partners include:

  * Google Adsense & Google AdManager
  * Googe Analytics  

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on scalemates.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies _(such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons)_ may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

scalemates.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. scalemates.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

#### **Google & DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on scalemates.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to scalemates.com and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

#### Google Analytics

scalemates.com is currently conducting market research in conjunction with Google Analytics. <http://www.google.com/analytics/en-GB/tos.html> (see section 8 for privacy related info)

#### Disable Cookies

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

### **Links to Independent Websites**

Articles, forum topics and comments hosted on scalemates.com may link to independently run web sites outside of the https://www.scalemates.com domain. scalemates.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such web sites.

### More info

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at tim@scalemates.com or using the contact form.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address.
